[
{"question" : "Different ways to create/initialize the local repository" , "a" : " Git pull" ,"b" : "Git clone" , "c":"git fork" ,"d" : "all of the above" , "correctAns" : "Git clone"}, 
	
{"question" : "In git diverging from the line of devolopment and continueing to do work without messing with that main line is known as" , 
"a" : "Merging" ,"b" : "Staging" , "c":"Branching" ,"d" : "Pulling" , "correctAns" : "Branching"}, 
	
{"question" : " steps in git to initialize a the remore repo" ,
 "a" : "Add" ,"b" : "Init" , "c":"Push" ,"d" : "commit" , "correctAns" : "Init"}, 


	{"question" : "What git status does?" , 
    "a" : "Display which files are and are not tracked" ,"b" : "Display impoformation regarding the commited project theory" ,
     "c":"All of the above" ,"d" : "None of the above" , "correctAns" : "Display which files are and are not tracked"}, 


	{"question" : "Valid attrubutes of a <table>" , "a" : "Cell pading" ,"b" : "Cellspacing" , "c":"Border" ,"d" : "All of the above" , "correctAns" : "All of the above"}, 
	
    {"question" : "Chose the list of proper self closing tags" ,
     "a" : "img" ,"b" : "br" , "c":"a href" ,"d" : "br" , "correctAns" : "br"}, 

	{"question" : "<form> method that sends data to to the destination resource in a secured way" , "a" : "Post" ,
    "b" : "Head" , "c":"delete" ,"d" : "Get" , "correctAns" : "Post"}, 

	{"question" : "Chose the list of proper self closing tags" , "a" : "Hr" ,"b" : "form" , "c":"Img" ,"d" : "All of the above" , "correctAns" : "hr"}, 
	{"question" : "Tags that acts as a container of other tags" , "a" : "img" ,"b" : "p" , "c":"div" ,"d" : "span" , "correctAns" : "div"}, 
	{"question" : "How many parts are box model" , "a" : "Padding" ,"b" : "Border" , "c":"Margin" ,"d" : "all of the above" , "correctAns" : "all of the above"}, 
	{"question" : "In which module property of @ngModel browsermodel is configured" , "a" : "Declerations" ,"b" : "Bootstrap" , "c":"Providers" ,"d" : "imports" , "correctAns" : "imports"} 


		





]